[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Are you avoiding me?
Mikoy!
No, I didn't know it was you.
How are you?
I didn't tell anyone that you're my informant.
But I need your help.
So Dad's death won't be for nothing.
Yes, bro.
Sir, I'm very disappointed that you left me behind here.
I thought it was supposed to be until the end of time.
What happened to the GAGO?
If I still have feelings for her?
You know, honestly, I don't know.
But I don't care.
Because all my heart wants right now
is to get justice for what she did to my father.
So tell me, Agent Alex,
that you can do
what needs to be done when the time comes.
I will.
Thank you.
Alex, let's go.
Enough, you two.
We already have enough internal squabbles in our world.
Let's not make things worse.
So here's the deal.
Papa, just let him be.
They told me that the first to arrive
at the meeting place will be his father.
They only have one request.
Just me and Chiara and a few bodyguards,
in order to not attract attention.
With me and La Fornarina there,
they won't stand a chance.
Just the two of us,
we can easily take out an entire battalion of their goons.
You're being way too overconfident, Rahmboy.
They can't kill us.
I also activated our lines at the embassy,
just in case we need diplomatic intervention.
We must protect our agents.
Sir. We're here to monitor and make sure there are no problems.
We have a local militia group that we could activate
if Agent Mikoy and Agent Alex need reinforcements.
Sir, like Yancy said,
we're here,
as an additional tool at your disposal, sir.
We don't need it, and we won't use it.
Okay?
Yes, sir. No problem.
Wait, why are we here?
They changed the meeting place at the last minute.
-Let's move. -Wait, Mikoy. Mikoy.
Are you sure?
The tracker says Francesco hasn't moved.
It could be a trap.
Alex, when you made me your police asset,
what made you so sure that I could be trusted?
We're the same, Alex.
I have complete faith in my asset.
That's why they keep changing locations.
We didn't scout the area, so we'll improvise.
You stay here on the ground.
Alex.
Be careful.
Let's go.
What's happening?
The Castellanis made some last-minute changes.
They changed the meeting place for Chiara.
It's possible.
Maybe they're afraid of Chiara too.
Let them be for now.
I don't have a clear shot.
If you don't have a shot,
I can move in.
-Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
They're going inside, Mikoy.
We can't rush this.
We haven't scouted the area yet.
You okay up there?
I'm okay.
You might be getting lonely up there.
Just say the word, okay?
Can you stop messing with me?
That's just like you.
Just trying to ease the tension.
You know, considering our situation.
Sometimes, you just can't control your heart.
Who knew I'd fall for a police asset?
Did you tell them that
we can hear their conversation on our comms?
That our signal is directly patched into their comms?
My assumption, sir, was that
I didn't need to tell them
because they already know that
this is standard operating procedure for missions like this.
Let's not act like high school kids getting all giddy.
Isolate this.
Try to…
I said keep it down.
They're saying something!
Never mind. They're having a moment!
-Sorry, sir. -Sorry, sir.
So, sir, should I mute it?
Listen in! But act professionally, okay?
Correct! Correct.
Alex, the Castellanis are moving. They're heading our way.
Let's go.
If Mikoy is there,
that means Alex is there too.
Is the back door safe?
There's no line of sight at the back.
All the open shots are in front.
Thank you.
-Okay? -Yes.
Be careful!
Because he's highly motivated to kill us all.
-You take the back door, okay? -But, Papa…
No buts, okay?
-Let's move. -Come on.
Be careful.
Is she a good shot?
She's better than a dead-eye shot.
Then we're good!
But here's what I want.
I want to be the one to finish Chiara.
Mikoy.
I want her to see me.
I want her to know that I'm the one who delivered justice for Dad,
and that I was the one who finished her.
So, what do you want me to do?
I need you to create a distraction.
Something good enough for me to get close to her.
How?
I know it sounds crazy,
but I need you
to leak our identities, Alex's and mine, to the Italians.
Mikoy!
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry up!
Let’s go, let's go.
Don’t worry, I’ll handle him.
What’s your plan?
Fix the problem without any noise.
Looks like we are not in Castellani’s radar now.
He spread a rumor about us escaping.
Seems like that asset of yours is trustworthy.
Sorry about what?
I'm sorry you weren't able to do what you were supposed to do here.
I have the rest of my life to make her pay for what she did.
Here’s my gift.
If you want to slice Mikoy’s neck.
We have another time for this.
For now, you have to go back to Alex.
What is it this time?!
What did you do?
Damn!